officesnapshots.com 2019-12-17

# Privacy Policy - Office Snapshots

Privacy Policy  
Effective Date: March 1, 2017

This Privacy Policy covers the officesnapshots.com website (hereinafter “Website”), which is owned and operated by Office Snapshots LLC (“Office Snapshots”). Office Snapshots is committed to protecting the privacy of its users and wishes to maintain a safe and secure environment for all users of the Website. Please read the following Privacy Policy to understand how your personal information is treated. From time to time, Office Snapshots may offer new services and/or products that may require Office Snapshots to update this Privacy Policy. Please check back with us periodically. If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should contact Office Snapshots’ Privacy Administrator by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

This Privacy Policy answers the following questions for you regarding your privacy protection:

 **WHAT INFORMATION DOES OFFICE SNAPSHOTS COLLECT?**

Office Snapshots collects personal information from users for different purposes.  Information gathered online can be identified as either anonymous or identifiable.  Anonymous information is information that cannot be traced back to the individual.  Identifiable information is information that is specific to an individual.

Anonymous Information

Like many websites, the Website gathers certain information automatically and stores it.  This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, searches performed, browser types, Internet services providers (ISP), referring/exit pages, date/time stamps, and clickstream data. Office Snapshots uses this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, administer the Website, gather demographic information about its user base as a whole, and improve its level of service to you. Office Snapshots does not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

Personally Identifiable Information

To use certain features of the Website, a user must submit information via forms. For example, a user may submit photographs or post job listings through the Website. In either case, Office Snapshots will collect the following information: (i) name, (ii) email address, (iii) company name; (iv) company location, and (v) website address. The provision of this personal information is mandatory and if you choose not to submit the requested information, you will not be able to use the features of the Website that require submission of this information.

The Website may provide you with the opportunity to share content with another person. For this feature to work, Office Snapshots may need to collect or be provided with the username, name, and/or email address of the person with whom you want to share content.

 **DOES THE WEBSITE USE “COOKIES”?**

Yes, the Website uses cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user’s device to help us improve your access to the Website and identify repeat visitors. Cookies can also enable Office Snapshots to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience. Cookies are not linked to any personally identifiable information.

 **HOW DOES OFFICE SNAPSHOTS USE MY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?**

Personally identifiable information collected is used primarily for the purpose it is collected (e.g., contacting a user after submission of a photograph). Office Snapshots also may use a user’s email address as follows provided that the user grants his/her consent to such additional use:

  * in internal surveys to obtain feedback on aspects of Office Snapshots’ business;
  * to notify users of information Office Snapshots thinks may be of interest to them; and
  * to send communications or promotional materials.

Office Snapshots may also use personal information collected to contact users in connection with the inappropriate use of the Website.

 **DOES OFFICE SNAPSHOTS DISCLOSE MY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?**

From time to time, Office Snapshots may disclose your personal information to organizations that perform services for or on behalf of Office Snapshots, for example to provide customer service, for research, marketing, data processing, and to measure the use of the Website. Office Snapshots will share with these companies only that personal information which they need to work on our behalf. Some of these service providers may be located in other countries. Your personal information will be provided to these organizations only if they agree to use such information solely for the purpose of providing services to Office Snapshots, and under the instructions of Office Snapshots, and with respect to that information, to act in a manner consistent with the relevant principles articulated in this Privacy Policy.

 **IS MY PERSONAL INFORMATION SECURE?**

The Website has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that we obtain from you, but we make no assurances about Office Snapshots’ ability to prevent any such loss, misuse, or alteration to you or to any third party. Please review Office Snapshots’ Terms of Service regarding Office Snapshots’ liability for any loss, misuse, or alteration of personally identifiable information.

 **CAN I UPDATE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED ABOUT ME?**

You have the right to correct and update the personal information collected about you through the Website by way of submitting a new form, sending an email, or clicking on the link in email newsletters sent to you.

 **WILL YOU NOTIFY ME IN THE EVENT OF CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY?**

Office Snapshots reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. In the event of a material change in our information collection and handling practices, Office Snapshots will inform those users who have provided an email address via email. Any changes will apply prospectively only.

 **HOW CAN I OPT-OUT FROM RECEIVING EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS?**

Office Snapshots provides you the opportunity to “opt-out” of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes when we ask for this information. For example, if you opted-in to receive marketing communications but no longer wish to receive communications from us, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication.

 **LINKS**

The Website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that Office Snapshots is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. Office Snapshots encourages users to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Office Snapshots.

 **NOTICE REGARDING CHILDREN**

The Website is general audience website and does not direct any of its content specifically at children under 13 years of age. We understand and are committed to respecting the sensitive nature of children’s privacy. If we learn or have reason to suspect that a user is under age 13, we will promptly delete any personal information for that user.

 **NOTICE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS**

Office Snapshots does not disclose your information to third parties for marketing purposes. If you are a California resident, you have the right to receive (a) information identifying all third-party companies to which we may have disclosed, within the past year, personal information pertaining to you and your family for those companies’ direct marketing purposes; and (b) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. To obtain such information, please email [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

 **CALIFORNIA DO NOT TRACK DISCLOSURE**

Office Snapshots does not track its customers over time and across third party websites to provide targeted advertising and therefore does not respond to Do Not Track (“DNT”) signals. However, some third parties do track of your browsing activities. If you are visiting third party websites, your browser should allow you to set the DNT signal on your browser so that third parties know you do not want to be tracked.

 **INTERNATIONAL USERS**

Office Snapshots is a U.S. company and the Website is hosted in the United States. If you access the Website from the European Union, Asia, or any other region, country, or jurisdiction with privacy laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure that differ from United States privacy laws, please note that, by your continued use of the Website, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer. In addition, you understand that your personal information may be processed in countries (including the United States) where privacy laws may be less stringent than in your country.

 **REQUIRED DISCLOSURES**

Office Snapshots may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our site.

 **HOW DO I CONTACT OFFICE SNAPSHOTS ABOUT PRIVACY CONCERNS?**

If you have any further questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
